// autogenerated file - DO NOT EDIT THIS FILE UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
// OR FACE YOUR DOOM!!
//encoding = RAW

tagInstaller01=It was between the Tigris and Euphrates rivers that Mesopotamia, the first great civilization, arose.  Over thousands of years, Mesopotamian cities formed and grew into powerful, sovereign city states.  Perhaps greatest of these was Babylon, famed for its walls and gates, its code of laws, and the miraculous Hanging Gardens.
tagInstaller02=For thousands of years, the Pharaohs of Egypt ruled over a kingdom tied by life and death to the river Nile.  It fed them and bathed them and shielded them from the harsh, barren deserts which huddled close to either side.  With the wealth and power the Nile granted, the Egyptians built palaces, temples, and pyramids - haunting landmarks that have long outlasted their makers.
tagInstaller03=It was among the Ancient Greeks that philosophy, science, math, history and the arts as we know them first began.  The independent city-states of Greece fished and farmed, dreamed and wrote poetry, warred against outsiders and amongst themselves, and observed and pondered life - leaving a legacy that would be admired and imitated the world over.
tagInstaller04=For thousands and thousands of years in China, humble peasants threw bones into the fire to predict the future, artisans carved jade, wood or ivory, and learned men painted and wrote with brush pens on rice paper.  When the Qin Emperor, Shi Huangdi, brought all China under one rule, could he have imagined how long his kingdom would endure, rarely troubled and ever mighty?
tagInstaller05=Standing high atop the rocky acropolis of Athens, the Parthenon was built as a gift to the goddess Athena after the Greeks defeated the invading forces of the mighty Persian Empire.  It was the general and statesman Pericles himself who took the wealth of the Athens-led Delian League and built this monument, which stands in Athens to this very day.
tagInstaller06=Amidst the desert sands of the Giza Plateau stand three mighty pyramids, tombs to the Pharaohs Khufu, Khafre, and Menkaure.  The greatest pyramids in Egypt were built when Pharaohs had the greatest power over their kingdoms and, in Khufu's case, were cruelest to their subjects.  Countless slaves would labor for years to build a pyramid, which were often started long before a Pharaoh's old age.
tagInstaller07=Thebes was the high capital of upper - or Southern - Egypt, and the throne of all the land during the Middle and New Kingdoms.  Its patron gods, different than the more familiar northern ones, were Amun, Mut, and Khonsu.  Among the many remarkable and timeless structures of Thebes are the Temples of Hatshepsut, Seti, and Luxor, as well as the more than sixty royal tombs in the Valley of the Kings.
tagInstaller08=Not a trace remains of Babylon's Hanging Gardens, one of the Seven Wonders of the World.  The terraced gardens were built by the great king Nebuchadnezzar for his homesick wife, Amyitis, and were filled with flowers, herbs and trees from her land of birth.
tagInstaller09=Since nearly the dawn of human civilization, fearless and enterprising merchants have crossed the mountainous spine of the Himalayas to bring spices, cloths, and other precious materials between the lands of the East and the Mediterranean - and beyond.  Wealth, art, ideas and beliefs all have traveled from west to east and east to west along the famed Silk Road.
tagInstaller10=A colossal defense against barbarous invaders, the great wall protects four thousand miles of China's northern border.  Dotted with watch-towers, barracks and gates, the wall was begun by the great emperor Shi Huangdi, and has been built and rebuilt in different eras over the course of Chinese history. 
tagInstaller11=In death as in life, the emperor Shi Huangdi did everything on a grand scale.  The unifier of China ordered that a literal army of terra cotta soldiers be buried with him on his death.  The eight thousand clay figures were life-sized and buried in marching ranks, prepared for conquest in whatever dark lands of the after-life their ruler found himself.
tagInstaller12=The Spartans were famed in Ancient Greece as rivals of Athens and as the greatest of Greek soldiers.  Spartans lived simple and rigorous lives, and were trained in athletics and warfare from a childhood.  Even girls received education and athletic training, a rare privilege in ancient times.  
tagInstaller13=The first among the Greek gods were the children of the titan Kronos.  To Hera and Zeus belonged the heavens, to Demeter the Earth, Poseidon the sea, and Hades ruled over the land of the dead.  Many a Greek tale tells how the first gods and their children, such as Athena, Apollo, and Hephaestus, courted, befriended, and took angry vengeance on mortal humans and each other.
tagInstaller14=The majestic palace of Knossos on the island of Crete is, in fact, much older than Classical Greece, although little is known of its origins or the people who built it.  The Ancient Greeks told myths of King Minos II, who ruled Crete in Knossos.  After earning the displeasure of the god Poseidon, he was given a son with a bull's head - the minotaur.  It is said that the great architect Daedalus built a labyrinth beneath the castle for this brutish and violent son, who devoured many an unlucky human sacrifice until the hero Theseus braved the maze and slew him.
tagInstaller15=Although there were many oracles in Ancient Greece, the Oracle of Delphi was the greatest and most famous.  Residing in the Temple of Apollo beside Mount Parnassus, the Oracle was thought to speak with the voice of the god Apollo himself.  Figures out of myth and history have paid visits to the Oracle, including Herakles, Oedipus, King Croesus of Lydia, and the philosopher Socrates.  Inscribed above the oracle were two phrases:  "Nothing in excess" and "Know thyself".
tagInstaller16=The gods that the people of Ancient Egypt worshipped were the mysterious masters of magic and wisdom.  The gods and their magic was everywhere.  The falcon-headed god Horus was in every falcon.  He was even present in a falcon statue.  When Egyptians depicted the demon snake Apep, they would always draw a benevolent god next to it.  Otherwise, Apep's image might get loose!
tagInstaller17=Although he was a titan, Prometheus fought on the side of the gods in the great war.  He was the most clever and ingenious of his kind, and it was he who created humans.  He looked after his creations, stealing some fire for them from the gods on Olympus when they were cold and helpless on the earth.  Prometheus taught them to burn sacrifices to appease the gods and win them to their side.  All the same, the gods were furious at his theft, and his punishment was painful and severe.
tagInstaller18=The primeval gods Apsu and Tiamat planned to destroy the younger gods, who had grown strong and arrogant in their eyes.  When Ea learned of this, he found and slew Apsu.  Tiamat, angry at her husband's death, made from herself an army of hideous monsters for revenge against the young gods.  Seeing the threat of their demise, a call was sent out among the gods, and it was Marduk, Ea's son, who emerged as champion.  He fought and slew Tiamat, and dispersed her army, taking from her the powerful Tablets of Destiny.
tagInstaller19=The Ancient Chinese believed that in the heavens dwelt the great and noble benefactors of the world.  First were the three:  Fuxi, Nuwa, and Shen-Nong.  These immortals helped humans gather into families, villages and kingdoms, and taught them writing, farming, fishing, and the other useful skills of civilization.  Fu Xi and Nuwa were said to be husband and wife, and Shennong was as a brother to the Yellow Emperor.
tagInstaller20=The Yellow Emperor was said to have come into being just after the world began.  Some say that he fashioned humankind out of clay.  It is also said that he invented traditional medicine, the compass, and silk cultivation.  The Yellow Emperor took the dragon as his symbol, and because he is considered to be the forefather of all the Han people, they have called themselves "the descendants of the dragon." 
tagXfire01=Xfire keeps track of when and where gamers are playing PC games online and lets their friends join them easily. It eliminates the hassles of running multiple programs like IRC, instant messengers, or in-game friends lists to keep track of when and where your friends are playing.
tagXfire02=
tagXfire03=Yes I want to install Xfire.
tagXfire04=No, I do not want to install Xfire at this time.
tagLauncher01=Install
tagLauncher02=Play Titan Quest
tagLauncher03=Read Me
tagLauncher04=Extras
tagLauncher05=Support
tagLauncher06=Uninstall
tagLauncher07=Exit
tagLauncher08=THQ Website
tagLauncher09=Official Titan Quest Website
tagLauncher10=Titan Quest Vault Website
tagLauncher11=Supreme Commander Website
tagLauncher12=THQ Customer Service
tagLauncher13=Monday through Friday, 9:00am to 5:00pm Pacific Time
tagLauncher14=For technical support outside the US please see the Read Me file 
tagLauncher15=Play Game
tagLauncher16=Register
tagLauncher17=Register Online
tagInstallerText01=Estimated time left:
tagInstallerText02=Transfer rate: 
tagInstallerText03=Cancel
tagInstallerText04=Setup Status
tagInstallerText05={%P} is configuring your new software installation.
tagInstallerText06=Titan Quest Installation Directory
tagInstallerText07=Titan Quest License Agreement
tagInstallerText08=User Information
tagInstallerText09=Enter your registration information.
tagInstallerText10=CD &Key:
tagInstallerText11=Installation Progress
tagInstallerText12=Install XFire
tagInstallerText13=Install to : 
tagInstallerText14=Add Start shortcut to folder : 
tagInstallerText15={%P} Desktop Shortcut
tagInstallerText16=Add shortcut to desktop.
tagInstallerText17=Remove character data and save game files.
tagInstallerText18=The install path must be less than 200 characters long.
tagInstallerText19=Your system does not meet the minimum system requirements.
tagInstallerText20=The installer has detected that the current system does not meet the minimum specifications. Do you wish to continue installation anyway?
tagInstallerText21=The installer has detected that the current system does not meet the minimum specifications and will be unable to run Titan Quest.  Please upgrade the system before attempting to install again.
tagInstallerText22=The system cannont uninstall Titan Quest while it is running.  Please quit the application before uninstalling.
tagInstallerText23=Unable to launch {%S0}
tagInstallerText24=InstallShield has encountered an error.
tagInstallerText25=DirectX 9.0c or later is needed to run this game.  Do you wish to install it?
tagInstallerText26=Please Insert the Disc:
tagInstallerText27=Titan Quest Disc 1
tagInstallerText28=Titan Quest Disc 2
tagInstallerText29=Titan Quest Disc 3
tagInstallerText30=Titan Quest Disc 4
tagInstallerText31=Titan Quest Disc 5
tagInstallerText32=Titan Quest Play Disc
tagInstallerText33=Titan Quest Install Disc
tagInstallerText34=Titan Quest DVD
tagInstallerText35=The current system does not meet the minimum graphics card specifications and will be unable to run Titan Quest.  Please upgrade the system before attempting to run again.
tagInstallerText36=You must install Titan Quest from an account with administrator priveledges.
tagPatcher01=Titan Quest Updater
tagPatcher02=Update Failed
tagPatcher03=Update Successful
tagPatcher04=Updating Titan Quest ...
tagPatcher05=Progress
tagPatcher06=Do you wish to update Titan Quest?
tagPatcher07=Cancel
tagPatcher08=Finish
tagPatcher09=Yes
tagPatcher10=No
tagPatcher11=Ok
tagPatcher12=The Titan Quest Updater has encountered an error.
tagPatcher13=Please restart Titan Quest and try to update again.
tagPatcher14=File CRC check failed.  Patch aborted.
tagPatcher15=This patch cannot be applied to this version of Titan Quest.
tagPatcher16=Version Mismatch
tagPatcher17=Patch requires version :
tagPatcher18=Current version is :
tagPatcher19=Titan Quest is not installed.
tagPatcher20=Titan Quest is currently running.
